{
    "subject": "resource/Gard\u0113z\u012b_Sadaat",
    "predicate": "property/langs",
    "object": "\u2022 Urdu \u2022 Persian \u2022 Awadhi",
    "human_readable": "Gard\u0113z\u012b Sadaat speaks in Urdu, Persian, and Awadhi languages.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9749839901924133,
            "question": "Does Gard\u0113z\u012b Sadaat speak Awadhi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9374967217445374,
            "question": "What languages does Gard\u0113z\u012b Sadaat speak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9267042279243469,
            "question": "Which of these languages is NOT spoken by Gard\u0113z\u012b Sadaat: English, Urdu, Persian, Awadhi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9167031049728394,
            "question": "Besides Urdu, what other language is spoken by Gard\u0113z\u012b Sadaat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8759093880653381,
            "question": "List the languages spoken by Gard\u0113z\u012b Sadaat."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7265987992286682,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of words in Urdu, Persian, and Awadhi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6664131283760071,
            "question": "Are there any similarities between the grammar of Urdu, Persian, and Awadhi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6138784289360046,
            "question": "Where is Awadhi primarily spoken?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3770071566104889,
            "question": "What are the main dialects of Persian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3357642889022827,
            "question": "What language family does Urdu belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gard\u0113z\u012b Sadaat speaks in Urdu, Persian, and Awadhi languages.",
            "html": "dbpedia_587_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the main dialects of Persian?",
            "html": "dbpedia_587_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Awadhi primarily spoken?",
            "html": "dbpedia_587_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any similarities between the grammar of Urdu, Persian, and Awadhi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_587_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_587_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_587_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_587_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_587_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_587_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_587_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_587_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_587_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_587_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_587_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information does not provide any details about the language spoken by the Gard\u0113z\u012b Sadaat. It only mentions that Hallaur or Hallor is a town in Uttar Pradesh and that its residents are referred to as Hallauri, but no specific languages are listed for this community. Therefore, based on the given documents, the statement that Gard\u0113z\u012b Sadaat speaks Urdu, Persian, and Awadhi cannot be confirmed, making the answer \"no\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context to suggest that Gard\u0113z\u012b Sadaat speaks in Urdu, Persian, and Awadhi languages. The information provided mentions their origins from Gardez, Afghanistan, and their migration to South Asia but does not mention any specific language they speak or associate with those particular regions.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text focuses on the origins, migration patterns, and historical influence of Sayyid communities, particularly mentioning their presence in India and Pakistan. It highlights their linguistic diversity within those regions but doesn't specify that Gard\u0113z\u012b Sadaat  specifically speak Urdu, Persian, and Awadhi.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The provided context does not mention anything about the Gard\u0113z\u012b Sadaat speaking Urdu, Persian, or Awadhi languages.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}